[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "name": "Admin",
        "email": "admin@example.com",
        "password": "password123",
        "role": "admin",
        "securityQuestions": [
            {
                "id": "q1",
                "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre de tu primera mascota?",
                "answer": "Test"
            },
            {
                "id": "q2",
                "question": "¿En qué ciudad naciste?",
                "answer": "City"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "name": "Jane",
        "email": "analyst@example.com",
        "password": "password123",
        "role": "analyst",
        "securityQuestions": [
            {
                "id": "q1",
                "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre de tu primera mascota?",
                "answer": "Test"
            },
            {
                "id": "q2",
                "question": "¿En qué ciudad naciste?",
                "answer": "City"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "name": "Jim",
        "email": "developer@example.com",
        "password": "password123",
        "role": "developer",
        "securityQuestions": [
            {
                "id": "q1",
                "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre de tu primera mascota?",
                "answer": "Test"
            },
            {
                "id": "q2",
                "question": "¿En qué ciudad naciste?",
                "answer": "City"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "name": "Jill",
        "email": "designer@example.com",
        "password": "password123",
        "role": "designer",
        "securityQuestions": [
            {
                "id": "q1",
                "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre de tu primera mascota?",
                "answer": "Test"
            },
            {
                "id": "q2",
                "question": "¿En qué ciudad naciste?",
                "answer": "City"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "name": "Christian",
        "email": "christian@example.com",
        "password": "12345678",
        "role": "user",
        "securityQuestions": [
            {
                "id": "q1",
                "question": "¿Cuál es el nombre de tu primera mascota?",
                "answer": "Nest"
            },
            {
                "id": "q2",
                "question": "¿En qué ciudad naciste?",
                "answer": "Cancun"
            }
        ]
    }
]